<Document>
  # Clearance Level 3

  The following document lists the duties of Central Command Representatives.

  If you are not of security clearance level 3, please dispose of this document and report its existence to the NTR.

  # Nanotrasen Representative

  [bold]1.[/bold] The Nanotrasen Representative is expected to follow all orders from Central Command;

  [bold]2.[/bold] The Nanotrasen Representative is expected to ensure command is following all orders from Central Command;

  [bold]3.[/bold] If the orders are not followed, the Nanotrasen Representative is expected to discreetly terminate said Command member and ensure a proper coverup;

  [bold]4.[/bold] At times Nanotrasen may implant an agent into the command structure to enhance Nanotrasen's goals. The Nanotrasen Representative is expected to assist the agent while maintaining the plausible deniability of a Syndicate agent infiltrating the command structure.

  [bold]5.[/bold] The Nanotrasen Representative is expected to follow crew-facing Standard Operating Procedure in the presence of crew and lower clearance level Standard Operating Procedure in the presence of lower clearance level command;

  # Blueshield Officer

  [bold]1.[/bold] The Blueshield Officer is expected to protect all members of Command to a reasonable extent;

  [bold]2.[/bold] The Blueshield Officer is expected to protect the Nanotrasen Representative with their life;

  [bold]3.[/bold] The Blueshield Officer is expected to follow orders from the Nanotrasen Representative;

  [bold]4.[/bold] The Blueshield Officer is expected to assist the Captain in dealing with any anti-Nanotrasen sympathies;

  [bold]5.[/bold] The Blueshield Officer is expected to follow crew-facing Standard Operating Procedure in the presence of crew and lower clearance level Standard Operating Procedure in the presence of lower clearance level command;

  # Internal Affairs Agent

  [bold]1.[/bold] The Internal Affairs Agent is expected to follow all orders from Central Command;

  [bold]2.[/bold] The Internal Affairs Agent is expected to assist the Nanotrasen Representative in enforcing all Standard Operating Procedures and maintainingthe secrecy of classified Standard Operating Procedures;

  [bold]3.[/bold] The Internal Affairs Agent is expected to follow crew-facing Standard Operating Procedure in the presence of crew and lower clearance level Standard Operating Procedure in the presence of lower clearance level command;
</Document>
